{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Interior Trim \u0026 Crown Molding Repair Pros","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40014/":{"taskOID":40014,"originalTaskOID":40014,"setID":338,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4571,"questionDisplayText":"Repairs Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be done? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6986,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window casing","answerDisplayText":"Window casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2004,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door casing","answerDisplayText":"Door casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6745,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wall molding (paneling, wainscoting, and chair rail)","answerDisplayText":"Wall molding (paneling, wainscoting, and chair rail)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1296,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ceiling molding (picture and crown)","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling molding (picture and crown)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2534,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Floor molding (baseboard, base shoe, and base cap)","answerDisplayText":"Floor molding (baseboard, base shoe, and base cap)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2475,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fireplace mantel","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace mantel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1216,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Cabinetry","answerDisplayText":"Cabinetry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1725,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Crown molding","answerDisplayText":"Crown molding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5009,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Railing","answerDisplayText":"Railing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5605,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Several small interior finish carpentry repair projects","answerDisplayText":"Several small interior finish carpentry repair projects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1553,"questionDisplayText":"Reasons for Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How was your finish trim damaged?  (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Attached remodel or construction","answerDisplayText":"Attached remodel or construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6925,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Weather","answerDisplayText":"Weather","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":599,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Accident","answerDisplayText":"Accident","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6924,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wear and tear","answerDisplayText":"Wear and tear","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6846,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water damage","answerDisplayText":"Water damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4657,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pests","answerDisplayText":"Pests","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":9,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4571,"questionDisplayText":"Repairs Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be done? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6986,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window casing","answerDisplayText":"Window casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2004,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door casing","answerDisplayText":"Door casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6745,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wall molding (paneling, wainscoting, and chair rail)","answerDisplayText":"Wall molding (paneling, wainscoting, and chair rail)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1296,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ceiling molding (picture and crown)","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling molding (picture and crown)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2534,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Floor molding (baseboard, base shoe, and base cap)","answerDisplayText":"Floor molding (baseboard, base shoe, and base cap)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2475,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fireplace mantel","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace mantel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1216,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Cabinetry","answerDisplayText":"Cabinetry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1725,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Crown molding","answerDisplayText":"Crown molding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5009,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Railing","answerDisplayText":"Railing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5605,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Several small interior finish carpentry repair projects","answerDisplayText":"Several small interior finish carpentry repair projects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6986,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Window casing","answerDisplayText":"Window casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2004,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door casing","answerDisplayText":"Door casing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6745,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Wall molding (paneling, wainscoting, and chair rail)","answerDisplayText":"Wall molding (paneling, wainscoting, and chair rail)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1296,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ceiling molding (picture and crown)","answerDisplayText":"Ceiling molding (picture and crown)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2534,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Floor molding (baseboard, base shoe, and base cap)","answerDisplayText":"Floor molding (baseboard, base shoe, and base cap)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2475,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fireplace mantel","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace mantel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1216,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Cabinetry","answerDisplayText":"Cabinetry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1725,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Crown molding","answerDisplayText":"Crown molding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5009,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Railing","answerDisplayText":"Railing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5605,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Several small interior finish carpentry repair projects","answerDisplayText":"Several small interior finish carpentry repair projects","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1553,"questionDisplayText":"Reasons for Damage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How was your finish trim damaged?  (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Attached remodel or construction","answerDisplayText":"Attached remodel or construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6925,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Weather","answerDisplayText":"Weather","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":599,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Accident","answerDisplayText":"Accident","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6924,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wear and tear","answerDisplayText":"Wear and tear","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6846,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water damage","answerDisplayText":"Water damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4657,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pests","answerDisplayText":"Pests","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Attached remodel or construction","answerDisplayText":"Attached remodel or construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6925,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Weather","answerDisplayText":"Weather","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":599,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Accident","answerDisplayText":"Accident","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6924,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wear and tear","answerDisplayText":"Wear and tear","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6846,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Water damage","answerDisplayText":"Water damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4657,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pests","answerDisplayText":"Pests","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":9,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40014/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40014,"taskName":"Interior Trim and Decorative Moldings - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Interior Trim and Decorative Moldings","xmTaskDescriptor":"Interior Trim \u0026 Crown Molding Repair Pros","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":251,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Carpenter Trim Molding carpentry structural","textMessagingName":"Repr Int Trim","rolloverLongDesc":"Finish carpenters have special skills \u0026 tools that allow them to precisely cut \u0026 install molding \u0026 trim so that the joints are tight \u0026 nearly invisible.  Typically, their work remains visible \u0026 they therefore pay keen attention to the aesthetic details, as opposed to rough or frame carpenters who are largely unconcerned with aesthetics.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes moldings, soffits \u0026 fascia.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Interior Trim and Decorative Moldings.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Crown Molding Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Interior Trim Contractors","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":9,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex or you have a variety of small projects, please ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"request a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Interior Trim \u0026 Moldings Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Interior Trim and Decorative Moldings - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Interior Trim Project","urlName":"Interior-Trim-and-Decorative-Moldings-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Crown Molding Repair Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Interior Trim Pros","searchKeywords":"trim, decorative, moulding, crown, cornice, baseboard, wainscoting, wainscoating, millwork, carpenter, carpentry, beadboard","emcCategoryOid":-12010,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":338,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}